(Raj:)Hey, Penny, can you
give me a hand with this?
(Sheldon:)Sure.
Aw, we had one of
these growing up.
(Penny:)I used to play
all the time.
(Raj:)Oh, yeah?
I love Ping-Pong.
(Penny:)Oh, I meant beer pong.
(Amy:)I had a table, too,
(Amy:)but I didn't have any friends,
so all I did was serve.
(Bernadette:)You know, you can leave one
side up and play against it.
(Amy:)And if I had a friend,
they might have told me that.
(Howard:)Excuse me.
(Howard:)Why is there a sticker on this?
(Howard:)It's my TARDIS
from Doctor Who.
(Howard:)I was planning on
moving it in the house.
(Bernadette:)I think you just answered
your own question.
(Howard:)Come on, one day,
this may double in value
(Howard:)and be worth half
what I paid for it.
(Bernadette:)Sweetie, we have a lot to do.
(Bernadette:)We don't need
to decide this right now.
(Howard:)Well, I guess as long as
you're keeping an open mind.
(Bernadette:)Of course.
♪ ♪